http://www.hardware.com/policies/privacy-policy/

BuySupportChatContactPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy1. Privacy and data protection Protecting your privacy is important to us because privacy and data protection is your human right. This Hardware.com Privacy Policy tells you how we collect your personal information and keep it confidential. In a nutshell, this means we will:Only collect and process your data when absolutely necessaryNot sell, rent or otherwise distribute or make public your personal informationCease to process your data at your requestRemove your personal information completely under your “right to be forgotton”2. LegislationAlong with our business and internal systems, this website is designed to comply with the following national and international legislation with regards to data protection and user privacy:UK Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA)EU Data Protection Directive 1995 (DPD)EU General Data Protection Regulation 2018 (GDPR)This site’s compliance with the above legislation, all of which are stringent in nature, means that this site is likely compliant with the data protection and user privacy legislation set out by many other countries and territories as well. If you are unsure about whether this site is compliant with your own country of residences’ specific data protection and user privacy legislation, please contact us for clarification using the details provided in section 11.3. Personal information that the Hardware.com website collects, why we collect it and how we collect itWe collect and use your personal information to provide you with:Convenient access to our products, events and servicesRelevant communications based on the information you have provided and that we determine to be of legitimate interest3.1 Site visitation trackingOur website uses Google Analytics (GA) to track user interaction. We use this data to determine the number of people using our site, to better understand how they find and use our web pages and to see their journey through the website.WHAT THIS MEANS TO YOU: although GA records data such as your geographical location, device, internet browser and operating system, none of this information personally identifies you to us. GA also records your computer’s IP address which could be used to personally identify you but Google do not grant us access to this. We consider Google to be a third party data processor (see section 5 below).GA makes use of cookies, details of which can be found on Google’s developer guides which are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser. Our website uses the analytics.js implementation of GA.The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether.Disabling cookies on your internet browser will stop GA from tracking any part of your visit to pages within our website.  However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Hardware.com’s most innovative and useful features and we recommend that you leave them turned on. If you do leave cookies turned on, be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.In addition to Google Analytics, this website may collect information (held in the public domain) attributed to the IP address of the computer or device that is being used to access it. The information is supplied to us from LeadForensics. The LeadForensics system does not use your IP address to identify you, the individual, in any way.*The LeadForensics system will only lookup information when a static IP address is being used. Differences between a static and dynamic IP address.More information about how LeadForensics uses IP addresses.3.2 Contact forms and email linksShould you choose to contact us using the contact form on our Contact us page or an email link like this one, the data will be collated into an email and sent to us over the Simple Mail Transfer Protocol (SMTP). Our SMTP servers are protected by TLS (sometimes known as SSL) meaning that the email content is encrypted using SHA-2, 256-bit cryptography before being sent across the internet. The email content is then decrypted by our local computers and devices.If you have explicitly opted-in to receive future marketing communications from us, the data you supply will be passed to and stored by Eloqua who we use as our email marketing suite. We consider Eloqua to be a third party data processor (see section 6 below). The email address that you submit will not be stored within this website’s own database or in any of our internal computer systems.WHAT THIS MEANS TO YOU: Your email address will remain within Eloqua’s database for as long as we continue to use Eloqua’s services for email marketing or until you specifically request removal from the list. You can do this by unsubscribing using the unsubscribe links contained in any communications that we send you or by requesting removal via email. When requesting removal via email, please send your email to us using the email account that is subscribed to the mailing list.3.3 Email communicationsIf you join our digital communications list, the email address that you submit will be forwarded to Eloqua who we use as our email marketing suite. We consider Eloqua to be a third party data processor (see section 5 below). The email address that you submit will not be stored within this website’s own database or in any of our internal computer systems.WHAT THIS MEANS TO YOU: Your email address will remain within Eloqua’s database for as long as we continue to use Eloqua’s services for email marketing or until you specifically request removal from the list. You can do this by unsubscribing using the unsubscribe links contained in any communications that we send you or by requesting removal via email. When requesting removal via email, please send your email to us using the email account that is subscribed to the mailing list.While you remain opted in, your email address remains within the Eloqua database and you will receive periodic communication from us.4. About this website’s serverThis website is hosted by LCN within a UK cloud server located in Hertfordshire.Full details of LCN’s cloud servers can be found here.5. Our third party data processorsWe use a number of third parties to process personal data on our behalf. These third parties have been carefully chosen and all of them comply with the legislation set out in section 2.0.Google (Privacy policy)Eloqua (Privacy policy)LeadForensics (Privacy Policy)6. Other third partiesHardware.com website contains links to other sites. Hardware.com does not share your personal information with these websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices.At times we may be required by law to disclose your personal information.7. Children’s PrivacyHardware.com’s business is not directed at minors and we do not promote or market our solutions or services to minors. If you believe that we have mistakenly or unintentionally collected Personal Information of a minor through our channels without appropriate consent, please notify us immediately using the contact details in section 11 so that we may immediately delete the information from the appropriate channels and make any other necessary corrections.8. Data breachesWe will report any unlawful data breach of this website’s database or the database(s) of any of our third party data processors to any and all relevant persons and authorities within 72 hours of the breach if it is apparent that personal data stored in an identifiable manner has been stolen.9. Your rightsYou may request to review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise modify any of your Personal Information that you have previously provided to us through the channels mentioned above, or object to the use or processing of such Personal Information by us at any time. If you have privacy concerns regarding access to or the correction of your Personal Information, please contact us using the details in section 11.10. Data controlThe data of this website is controlled by: ©2018 Hardware Group Ltd. Hardware Group Ltd. is a Private Limited Company. Registered in England & Wales, Registration Number: 8217633.11. Data Protection contact detailsData Compliance Hardware UK Wellington House Kemble Enterprise Park Cirencester GL7 6BQ United KingdomTelephone: +44 (0) 1285 771 660
Email: info@hardware.com12. Changes to our privacy policyWe may update this privacy policy from time to time inline with legislation or industry developments. We will not explicitly inform you of these changes. Instead, we recommend that you check this page occasionally for any policy changes.This policy was last reviewed and updated on the 10th April 2018.  Policies are periodically reviewed to ensure compliance with the current compliance environment.  View More Policies >    By using this site, you confirm you understand and accept Hardware's privacy policy and cookie policy. OKPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are as essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Advanced NetworkingCore Networks & InfrastructureData CentreOrchestration & AutomationVisibility & AnalyticsCloudConsultancy ServicesOptimisation and ManagementSecurity and ConnectivityCloud LicensingCompute & StoreCloud ReadyHybrid InfrastructureOn-premiseSoftware SolutionsSecurityApplication SecurityEndpointNetwork Access ControlPerimeter and InternalServicesAsset Recovery & RepairGlobal LogisticsProfessional ServicesSupportAboutBlogCareersContactCustomersTeam HardwareStoreMedicalLogin for Support
